<resources>
    <string name="app_name">UzbekCoders</string>
    <string name="translate_google">Google Translate – Google Play ilovalarihttps://play.google.com › store › apps › details › id=co... Text translation: Translate between 108 languages by typing • Tap to Translate: Copy text in any app and tap the Google Translate icon to translate (all ... DeepL Translate: The world\'s most accurate translatorhttps://www.deepl.com › translator See why millions translate with DeepL every day. Fast, accurate, and secure – translate texts and full document files instantly. Google Translate - Chrome Web Storehttps://chrome.google.com › ... Shu sahifani tarjima qilish 13-avg, 2021 — Highlight or right-click on a section of text and click on Translate icon next to it to translate it to your language. Or, to translate the ... Google Translate 4+ - App Store - Applehttps://apps.apple.com › app Shu sahifani tarjima qilish Download Google Translate and enjoy it on your iPhone, iPad, and iPod touch. ... Text translation: Translate between 108 languages by typing. Change Chrome languages translate webpages - Androidhttps://support.google.com › ... Shu sahifani tarjima qilish Translate webpages in Chrome · On your Android phone or tablet, open the Chrome app Chrome · Go to a webpage written in another language. · At the bottom, select ... Google Translate User Guides\'ni sotib oling - Microsofthttps://www.microsoft.com › uz-latn-uz › google-transl... 3-fev, 2021 — Google Translate is a very useful tool that can translate words and sentences from one language to another. It supports multiple languages ... Значение translate в английскомhttps://dictionary.cambridge.org › ... Shu sahifani tarjima qilish 4 kun oldin — translate sth into sth You can\'t just translate an English website into Spanish and assume it will still be effective. be translated into sth ... ngx-translate/core - (i18n) library for Angular - GitHubhttps://github.com › core Shu sahifani tarjima qilish Installation. First you need to install the npm module: npm install @ngx-translate/core --save. Choose the version corresponding to your Angular version: ... Listen, Read or Translate with Recite Me - Orkney Islands ...https://www.orkney.gov.uk › ... Shu sahifani tarjima qilish Translate web pages into over 100 languages, many with speech. On-screen text magnifier to assist users with visual impairments. Audio generator converts text ... Aloqador qidiruvlar</string>
</resources>